this tutorial is about moving arms which
本教程是关于移动手臂的
这是一个非常微妙的机制
this tutorial is about moving arms which
is a very subtle mechanism which has
最多的变化和使用最多
基本是基于平行四边形
is a very subtle mechanism which has
numerous variations and uses the most
我们在教程5中介绍了
绿色位是平行四边形
numerous variations and uses the most
basic is based on the parallelogram
黄色的位是基本的动臂
粉红色的位在手臂上加了一个肘
basic is based on the parallelogram
which we cover in tutorial 5 here it is
这使得运动看起来更加如此
这是基本的变化
which we cover in tutorial 5 here it is
the green bit is the parallelogram the
这个例子是基本的平行四边形
您可以看到四个动臂
the green bit is the parallelogram the
yellow bit is a basic moving arm the
四肢或略微向内移动
不同的方向，如果我们看
yellow bit is a basic moving arm the
pink bit is adding an elbow to the arm
兰普和科夫斯基的鬼屋
这有一个很好的例子，所以
pink bit is adding an elbow to the arm
which makes appear to move even more so
这是平行四边形这是两个
移动手臂，使其中一个移动
which makes appear to move even more so
this is the basic variation here's an
在页面上，您会看到相同的内容
卡的一面一直
this is the basic variation here's an
example this is the basic parallelogram
通过另一片翻转
平行四边形有两个小
example this is the basic parallelogram
you can see that with four moving arms
三角形，这取决于哪个三角形
你坚持下去如果你坚持下去
you can see that with four moving arms
on it four limbs or moving in slightly
一个在另一边
平行四边形就是
on it four limbs or moving in slightly
different directions if we look at the
相对页面旋转，因此
真的最有用的其他小
different directions if we look at the
the haunted house by Lampe and Kowski
三角形就是那个
那辆车翻过来
the haunted house by Lampe and Kowski
this has got a really good example so
平行四边形也在此处形成沟壑
它连接页面的位置，因此您可以粘贴
this has got a really good example so
here's the parallelogram here are two
为此而动臂
这是一个例子，这是基本的
here's the parallelogram here are two
moving arms so one of them moves rotates
平行四边形这是动臂
我们已经看了另外两个
moving arms so one of them moves rotates
against the page and you see the same
小三角形卡在这个沟中
由平行四边形加入
against the page and you see the same
side of the piece of card all the way
页面，所以这两个有两个移动
手臂被卡住，如您所见
side of the piece of card all the way
through the other piece flips over on
打开和关闭它有一个不同的
动作，这是另一个例子
through the other piece flips over on
the parallelogram there are two small
这是使用这种类型的机制吗
所以平行折叠到
the parallelogram there are two small
triangles and it depends which triangle
页面，我们被卡住了小三角形
在，所以这些都让我们感动
triangles and it depends which triangle
you stick it to if you stick it to this
手臂朝着不同的方向运动
有很多方法可以做到这一点
you stick it to if you stick it to this
one which is on the small side of the
用过，所以这是一个非常复杂的
所以这是基本的跳跃
one which is on the small side of the
parallelogram that is the one that
我刚刚告诉你的数字
其中两个有两个平行四边形
parallelogram that is the one that
rotates against the page so that's
与这些跳跃彼此建立
算出其他变化，这是
rotates against the page so that's
really the most useful the other small
类型，所以这实际上是移动
手臂从面具后面出现，所以
really the most useful the other small
triangle that's the one that will make
绿色位是一个大的平行四边形，
手臂实际上粘在页面上
triangle that's the one that will make
the the piece of car flip over the
角度使它运动
当它打开和关闭时，这是
the the piece of car flip over the
parallelogram also creates a gully here
如果你看看它的另一种变化
这样一来，您会看到那些
parallelogram also creates a gully here
where it joins the page so you can stick
绿色里面有一个平行四边形
一个只是一个面具，然后有一个
where it joins the page so you can stick
moving arms in for that
平行四边形与移动
手臂粘在上面，而不是看到
here's an example here's the basic
整个机制及其运作方式
只是看到图像从后面出现
here's an example here's the basic
parallelogram this is the moving arm
绿色面具后面
所以我只做其中之一
parallelogram this is the moving arm
we've already looked at here's two more
你可以看到如何制作它，你需要一个
卡片的底页将其对折
we've already looked at here's two more
small triangles stuck into this gully
彻底弄皱，需要一块
使平行四边形与
small triangles stuck into this gully
created by the parallelogram joining the
一张像这样折的卡
两端各有一个折痕
created by the parallelogram joining the
page and so these two have two moving
好吧，我们在这里制作平行四边形
如教程5中所述，所以您只需
page and so these two have two moving
arms stuck on and so as you see as you
折叠一个额外的平行折痕，这样
现在你得到的是
arms stuck on and so as you see as you
open and close it they have a different
三个平行的折痕
一面和短面，以便找出
open and close it they have a different
action and here's another example this
你把这个贴在哪里
您只需要在页面上标记一个
action and here's another example this
is this is using that type of mechanism
的褶皱所在，所以我只标记
短边的能力，然后
is this is using that type of mechanism
so is the parallel fold through to the
你要把它翻转过来
遮住并留长边
so is the parallel fold through to the
page and we've got small triangles stuck
这将为您提供基本的
平行四边形，但在我们这样做之前
page and we've got small triangles stuck
in and so those are giving us moving
您还有另外一组折痕
做两个小三角形，这是
in and so those are giving us moving
arms are moving in different directions
您的卡这​​就是您的折痕
顶部边缘向下，所以它是齐平的
there are numerous ways that this can be
有那个折痕所以很红
折痕在那里然后折回去
there are numerous ways that this can be
used so here's a really complicated one
本身，是的，只是将其推入
确保一切正常
used so here's a really complicated one
so this is this is the basic jumping
再折回去，所以现在
确保两个小
so this is this is the basic jumping
figure that I just showed you got those
三角形在顶部被卡住了
在页面底部附近粘贴
figure that I just showed you got those
two of them there's two parallelograms
您为标记所做的长边
较短的一面，以便页面平整时
two of them there's two parallelograms
built onto each other with these jumping
平行四边形平放，所以您可以
同时粘贴两个标签
built onto each other with these jumping
figures other variations there's this
有胶水
对，所以用折痕压住它
figures other variations there's this
type so this is actually the the moving
做到这一点，以便
整个东西都是平整的
type so this is actually the the moving
arm appears from behind a mask so the
应与脊柱折叠平行
它关闭确保前进
arm appears from behind a mask so the
green bit is a big parallelogram and the
确保现在一切正常
您可以将它们弹出来，这就是
green bit is a big parallelogram and the
arm is actually stuck to the page at an
基本的潜在机制
平行四边形有两个小小的
arm is actually stuck to the page at an
angle that's what gives it the movement
添加三角形，然后您将
移动手臂，这样就适合
angle that's what gives it the movement
as it opens and closes and here's
短边，所以很适合
在那个三角形上，你可以修剪
as it opens and closes and here's
another variation of it if you look at
那里放了一点胶水
正确地粘在那里
another variation of it if you look at
it this way around you'll see those
我到这儿来的东西太久了
关闭将紧缩
it this way around you'll see those
there's a parallelogram inside the green
脊椎，所以我只剪一块
如果合适的话，现在很合适
there's a parallelogram inside the green
one is just a mask and then there's a
如果需要的话，可以在参数中很好地
让它给你额外的肘部
one is just a mask and then there's a
parallelogram inside with the moving
可以从车上切下来
粘上
parallelogram inside with the moving
arms stuck to it rather than seeing the
所以这里有基本的动臂
这就是它的工作原理
arms stuck to it rather than seeing the
whole mechanism and how it works you
所以现在我将向您展示整个系列
书中其他例子的例子
whole mechanism and how it works you
just see the image appearing from behind
所有的变化都非常有用
机制，所以首先我们要知道的是
just see the image appearing from behind
behind the green mask
罗伯茨帮助非洲的动物
óbuda，所以在这里，我们有一个
so I'll just make one of those just so
动臂这是一个小的V型折
尾巴移动
so I'll just make one of those just so
you can see how to make it you'll need a
这样身体就成为一个
平行四边形运动臂
you can see how to make it you'll need a
base sheet sheet of card fold it in half
面具下面的头在
移动臂，使其打开和关闭
base sheet sheet of card fold it in half
crease thoroughly you need a piece to
头部移动是下一个
平行四边形支撑整个
crease thoroughly you need a piece to
make the parallelogram with so just a
斑马的头，我们有两个小
这里的三角形和下面的另一个
make the parallelogram with so just a
piece of card something like this fold
面具
所以当你打开和关闭它时，腿是
piece of card something like this fold
the tab onto each end of it crease them
他们是第三只动臂
这就是我可以显示的平行四边形
the tab onto each end of it crease them
well we're making a parallelogram here
这样一来，您可以看到
显然有平行四边形
well we're making a parallelogram here
as explained in tutorial 5 so you just
有平行四边形和图像
粘在移动的手臂上并摆动
as explained in tutorial 5 so you just
fold an extra parallel crease into it so
页面打开时，这是另一个
这是鸟的身体之一
fold an extra parallel crease into it so
now what you've ended up with you've got
平行四边形，你有两个
动臂让您运动
now what you've ended up with you've got
three parallel creases you've got a long
方向，这里的最后一个得到了
象头这样看你
three parallel creases you've got a long
side and the short side so to find out
可以很清楚地看到
与小三角形平行四边形
side and the short side so to find out
where you stick this put the piece on
在页面打开时为您提供操作
然后关闭下一个是博物馆
where you stick this put the piece on
the page you just need to mark where one
基思·摩尔的非自然历史
有平行四边形
the page you just need to mark where one
of the creases lies so I'll just mark
实际上这里有两个平行四边形
这里一个小，然后有一个
of the creases lies so I'll just mark
the the short side bilities and then
另一个在这里，一个给你
这个运动的手臂，这给了
the the short side bilities and then
you're going to flip this over flip it
你那一个，因为它关闭两个是
在一起
you're going to flip this over flip it
over and stick the long side to the mark
这是我的丛林弹出书
乌龟是平行四边形和
over and stick the long side to the mark
this will be giving you your basic
你有两个动臂来自
在面具后面，然后你有
this will be giving you your basic
parallelogram but before we do that
这两个尾鳍，如您所见
这是一种微妙的机制
parallelogram but before we do that
you've got one more set of creases to
你在各种方向上运动
这是我们这里的大猩猩
you've got one more set of creases to
make the two small triangles so here's
实际上这是一个浮动的游戏
这就是我们在教程12中介绍的内容
make the two small triangles so here's
your card here's your crease just fold
他们充当了手臂的面具
大猩猩移动，然后你有
your card here's your crease just fold
the top edge down so it's it's flush
另一个鳄鱼头熊猫
头所有这些都由
the top edge down so it's it's flush
with that with that crease so it's flush
动臂，这就是罗伯特的
圣诞节前一天晚上的布达
with that with that crease so it's flush
with that crease there and fold it back
他正在用动臂
实际上使车轮转动
with that crease there and fold it back
on itself and yeah just push it in just
在这里的例子中，您可以看到轮子是
都朝着不同的方向前进
on itself and yeah just push it in just
to make sure it's all working well so
所以这是另一个真正微妙的用途
给你的动臂给你
to make sure it's all working well so
fold it back again so there is so now
转动车轮好吧，这是一个小
红帽造纸工程公司
fold it back again so there is so now
making sure that the two little
布鲁斯·福斯特（Bruce Foster），这就是狼
狼的主体是一对
making sure that the two little
triangles are on the top this is stuck
平行四边形，然后是尾部和
后腿是推动我们前进的机制
triangles are on the top this is stuck
near the bottom of your page glue the
头和前脚是另一个
一个人打开和关闭，你就会得到
near the bottom of your page glue the
long side to the mark you made for the
可爱的创始机制，然后
最后，我从马修那里得到了妈咪
long side to the mark you made for the
shorter side so when the page is flat
Reinhart这是杰作，是
真的很棒的书，所以在这种传播
shorter side so when the page is flat
the parallelogram lies flat so you can
你有很多动臂
周围，​​但我真正喜欢的是
the parallelogram lies flat so you can
glue both tabs at the same time so
最后一个更大的你有头
武装他们正在移动的脚
glue both tabs at the same time so
there's the glue
不同的方式，这是一个非常聪明的
动臂的组合结构
right so stick that down with the crease
所以是绝对的杰作
你有婴儿的手臂
right so stick that down with the crease
to the mark do this one down so that the
挥舞着手臂挥舞着名字
这本书详细解释了
to the mark do this one down so that the
whole thing is flat all the creases
弹出式设计和纸张力学
您
whole thing is flat all the creases
should be parallel with the spine fold